Patrik Mulató

Personal info

Date of birth: 1998-07-08

Website: https://patrikmulato.github.io/

Nationality: Hungarian

Address: Garam 13, Miskolc 3528, Hungary

Phone number: 06204793310

Email address: mulatopatrik@gmail.com

Profile

Self-taught web developer who is seeking to learn and create new things. Have been coding for 2 years started with C# then learnt the fundamentals of Front-end web development and still improving himself day to day. Looking to join an organization where the opportunity for growth and personal development is embraced.

Skills

Front-end		Backend	
HTML5	••••	Node.js	••000
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)	••••	Express	••000
Javascript	••••	MongoDB	••000
Wordpress (WooCommerce)	•••00	git	

Experience

Csigu Kemence Miskolc

Web Developer

2018-01 - 2018-02

- Collaborated with clients from concept through final delivery of product or service.
- E-commerce site built with Opencart CMS
- Implemented Google Analytics and optimized SEO
- http://csigu.hu/

Kavegepdepo Miskolc

Web Developer

2018-03 - 2018-04

- First project with Wordpress CMS
- Multilingual (English Hungarian)
- Google analytics and SEO optimization
- http://kavegepdepo.com/

Education

Miskolci Egyetem Computer Science and Engineering 2017-09 – 2021-06

Miskolc In progress

Avasi Gimnázium High School 2017-05

Miskolc advanced final exam in IT

Code academy Web development

Completed courses (Sass, Javascript, Jquery, Node, Express)